<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jobs>
   <job>
      <title>Senior Software Engineer .NET/Java</title>
      <description>ACT-Canberra, • Exciting Defence related projects • Bring your strong .Net and Java skills to this interesting project • Based in Canberra, ACT As we look forward in 2016 and beyond, we anticipate we will enjoy strong growth and interesting challenges in supporting the Department of Defence to deliver information and communications technology (ICT) solutions via various programs. As a Senior Software Engineer y</description>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Senior-Software-Engineer-NET-Java-Job-Canberra-ACT-AU-167488523.aspx</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Senior Java Developer</title>
      <description>QLD-Brisbane, Opportunity of a lifetime! My client is a large global organisation and are leading providers of their services in the industry. They pride themselves in being thought leaders and provide great opportunities for growth and self development to their employees. By joining their organisation, you will be working on challenging projects in a supportive team. But you will need to be very autonomous to </description>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Senior-Java-Developer-Job-Brisbane-QLD-AU-167491297.aspx</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Senior Java Developer</title>
      <description>VIC-Melbourne, Work with the latest technology Exposure to some very recognsiable clients Industry training &amp; certifications Innovative Australian organisation is seeking passionate, experienced Developers to join an exciting phase Your new company This company prides itself on excellence utilising new technologies for cutting edge applications for some very recognisable clients. As they continue to grow, an opp</description>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Senior-Java-Developer-Job-Melbourne-VIC-AU-166533790.aspx</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Senior Java Developer</title>
      <description>QLD-Brisbane, 3 month contract Amazing hourly rates Brisbane CBD fringe location Seeking an experienced Senior Java Developer for a 3 month contract. Working on various parts of the business, you will be expected to hit the ground running. The role: You will be responsible for : learning the existing internal systems and improving them using Java, SOAP/ RESTFul Services, Spring/Hibernate/Java/PLSQL Developing t</description>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Senior-Java-Developer-Job-Brisbane-QLD-AU-166951651.aspx</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>AEM Developer - Java</title>
      <description>VIC-Melbourne, Permanent position CBD Location Work in an encouraging an open culture Join a leading consultancy and work with well recognised clients, support them with your experience with AEM Your new company This company prides itself on excellence utilising new technologies for cutting edge applications for some very recognisable clients. As they continue to grow, an opportunity has emerged for a strong AEM</description>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/AEM-Developer-Java-Job-Melbourne-VIC-AU-166536292.aspx</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Systems Developer - DevOps</title>
      <description>NSW-Sydney, Systems Developer - DevOps Job Number: 045260 Function Category Information Technology Primary Location New South Wales-Sydney Employment Type Permanent - Full time Description About this job Our Systems Developer - DevOps will be responsible for ensuring that applications are designed, developed, deployed and maintained in alignment with infrastructure capabilities and ING Direct’s operational co</description>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Systems-Developer-DevOps-Job-Sydney-NSW-AU-167773078.aspx</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Systems Developer - DevOps</title>
      <description>NSW-Sydney, Description About this job Our Systems Developer - DevOps will be responsible for ensuring that applications are designed, developed, deployed and maintained in alignment with infrastructure capabilities and ING Direct’s operational considerations Main responsibilities Provide code-line &amp; release branch management Support and improve continuous integration, release management models and processes </description>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Systems-Developer-DevOps-Job-Sydney-NSW-AU-167771737.aspx</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Analyst - Big data</title>
      <description>NSW-Sydney, An exceptional opportunity to excel your career in Big Data in a growing function that continues to develop &amp; leverage new technologies. About the Business &amp; Team CommBank is a leading provider of integrated financial services employing more than 52,000 people globally. We're proud of our iconic brand, scale and diversified business mix. We're built around a simple vision to 'To excel at securing </description>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Analyst-Big-data-Job-Sydney-NSW-AU-167769801.aspx</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Senior Analyst - Big Data</title>
      <description>NSW-Sydney, This role will be exposed to world class leading technology and techniques creating opportunities to be part of innovative and inspiring solutions. It is an opportunity to be a part of world class data analytics and infrastructure projects and further grow your technical and stakeholder capabilities. About the Business &amp; Team CommBank is a leading provider of integrated financial services employin</description>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Senior-Analyst-Big-Data-Job-Sydney-NSW-AU-167769802.aspx</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Solution Architect/Test Lead</title>
      <description>VIC-Melbourne, About The Role Immediate Start! We are looking for an experienced Technical Solution Architect with more than 10 years experience to join our team on a 12 month contract. This role will be key in understanding the technical aspects of the Programs current environment solution and track changes planned per releases, ensuring the integration component changes are appropriately tested to capacity and</description>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Solution-Architect-Test-Lead-Job-Melbourne-VIC-AU-167773046.aspx</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Junior Systems Administrator</title>
      <description>NSW-North Sydney, Career role North Sydney location Close to transport Our client is currently upgrading their existing computer system to a cloud-based environment. To facilitate the transfer from one system to another, our client is seeking to engage a Junior Systems Administrator who has either recently finished a TAFE Diploma course or a University degree and who may have had up to 6 months Systems Administrati</description>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Junior-Systems-Administrator-Job-North-Sydney-NSW-AU-167737248.aspx</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Front End Developer x3</title>
      <description>QLD-Brisbane, Multiple positions Industry leader Enterprise level, Agile development environment Attractive salary Convenient location Client Details An industry leader in the insurance space is currently expanding their online presence exponentially and taking on new exciting products. Driving the latest technologies and with the opportunity to work at the cutting edge of web development in an Enterprise, Agil</description>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Front-End-Developer-x3-Job-Brisbane-QLD-AU-167513939.aspx</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Application Software Engineer</title>
      <description>VIC-Bayswater North, The successful candidate will: Design and develop software features Work closely with the product owner to create and refine the product Write user stories Plan sprints and track sprint progress Improve readability, reduce complexity and improve maintainability of the code base Understand and apply modern software design Create unit tests for new and existing code participate in pair programming s</description>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Application-Software-Engineer-Job-Bayswater-North-VIC-AU-166570951.aspx</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Google Apps Support Engineer</title>
      <description>NSW-Sydney, Are you someone passionate about Google Apps and the value it can add to an organisation? Do you enjoy supporting others and delivering a memorable client experience? Must have GOOGLE APPS SUPPORT EXPERIENCE Client Details Our IT team provide enabling business technologies and information technology services that support Our client in meeting its overall strategic objectives. The success of our fu</description>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Google-Apps-Support-Engineer-Job-Sydney-NSW-AU-167237104.aspx</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Junior Systems Administrator</title>
      <description>NSW-North Sydney, Career role North Sydney location Close to transport Our client is currently upgrading their existing computer system to a cloud-based environment. To facilitate the transfer from one system to another, our client is seeking to engage a Junior Systems Administrator who has either recently finished a TAFE Diploma course or a University degree and who may have had up to 6 months Systems Administrati</description>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Junior-Systems-Administrator-Job-North-Sydney-NSW-AU-167484680.aspx</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Senior Software Engineer C++</title>
      <description>ACT-Canberra, • Exciting Defence related projects • Bring your strong C+ skills to this interesting project • Based in Canberra, ACT As we look forward in 2016 and beyond, we anticipate we will enjoy strong growth and interesting challenges in supporting the Department of Defence to deliver information and communications technology (ICT) solutions via various programs. As a Senior Software Engineer you will be </description>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Senior-Software-Engineer-C-Job-Canberra-ACT-AU-167488524.aspx</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Assistant Product Manager</title>
      <description>QLD-Brisbane, 3 month contract role with possible extension CBD fringe location Challenging role Working with a broad range of customers and clients, assist with the development and management of products and services including visualisation websites &amp; information portals. Assist customers transform large amounts of data into information that assists them to make business decisions. Key skills and responsibilit</description>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Assistant-Product-Manager-Job-Brisbane-QLD-AU-167232815.aspx</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Head Teacher - Coonamble High School</title>
      <description>70% rental subsidy applies, Years 7 - 12 (Full Time). Approval to teach science. 29/05/2016 - 01/07/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=8451</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Head Teacher - Gundagai High School</title>
      <description>Years 7 - 12 (Full Time). Approval to teach mathematics (Years 11 - 12), mathematics (Years 7 - 10) and mathematics extensions 1 &amp; 2. 18/07/2016 - 20/12/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=8442"</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Head Teacher - Ryde Secondary College</title>
      <description>Years 7 - 12 (Full Time). Approval to teach students with mild intellectual disability and moderate intellectual disability. 30/05/2016 - 20/12/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=8415"</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teacher - Brewarrina Central School</title>
      <description>90% rental subsidy applies, Years K - 12 (Full Time). Approval to teach infants (K - 2) and primary (3 - 6) and general. Willingness to teach visual arts. 06/06/2016 - 16/12/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=1350"</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teacher - Collarenebri Central School</title>
      <description>90% rental subsidy applies, Years K - 2 (Full Time). Approval to teach infants (K - 2) and infants (K - 2) and primary (3 - 6). 23/05/2016 - 20/12/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=1624"</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teacher - Coonamble High School</title>
      <description>70% rental subsidy applies, Years 7 - 12 (Full Time). Approval to teach learning and support K-12 and learning and support secondary. Willingness to teach learning and support K-12 and learning and support secondary. 30/05/2016 - 16/12/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=8451"</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teacher - Evans High School</title>
      <description>Years 7 - 12 (Full Time). Approval to teach technology mandatory (Years 7-8), industrial technology - metal and metal and engineering. 30/05/2016 - 16/12/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=8420"</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teacher - Georges River College Oatley Senior Campus</title>
      <description>Years 11 - 12 (Full Time). Approval to teach library. 30/05/2016 - 19/12/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=8284"</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teacher - John Brotchie Nursery School</title>
      <description>Years P - K (Full Time). Approval to teach pre-school. 18/07/2016 - 16/12/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=5423"</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teacher - Leeton High School</title>
      <description>50% rental subsidy applies, Years 7 - 11 (0.8 Part Time). Approval to teach mathematics (Years 7 - 10). Willingness to teach mathematics (Years 11 - 12). 30/05/2016 - 20/12/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=8156"</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teacher - Marsden High School</title>
      <description>Years 7 - 12 (Full Time). Approval to teach history (Years 7 - 10), Geography and society and culture/international studies. Willingness to teach studies of religion. 06/06/2016 - 19/08/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=8225"</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teacher - Molong Central School</title>
      <description>Years 7 - 12 (Full Time). Approval to teach English (Years 11 - 12) and English (Years 7 - 10). Willingness to teach history (years 7 - 10) and history (modern). 18/07/2016 - 20/12/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=2590"</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teacher - Quakers Hill East Public School</title>
      <description>Years K - 6 (Full Time). Approval to teach infants (K - 2) and primary (3 - 6). 06/06/2016 - 20/12/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=4212"</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teacher - Sylvania High School</title>
      <description>Years 7 - 11 (Full Time). Approval to teach technology mandatory (Years 7-8). Willingness to teach industrial technology - timber and industrial technology - multimedia/photography. 09/06/2016 - 29/07/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=8463"</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teacher - Tamworth High School</title>
      <description>Years 7 - 12 (Full Time). Approval to teach science and biology. 06/06/2016 - 17/12/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=8139"</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teacher - Ulladulla High School</title>
      <description>Years 7 - 12 (Full Time). Approval to teach English (Years 7 - 10) and English (Years 11 - 12). 08/08/2016 - 23/09/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=8495"</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teacher - Wattawa Heights Public School</title>
      <description>Years K - 6 (0.6 Part Time). Approval to teach primary (3 - 6). Willingness to teach infants (K - 2). 06/06/2016 - 20/12/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=4059"</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teacher - Wilcannia Central</title>
      <description>90% rental subsidy applies, Years P - 12 (Full Time). Approval to teach primary (3 - 6). 29/05/2016 - 18/12/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=3442"</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teacher - Willyama High School</title>
      <description>70% rental subsidy applies, Years 7 - 12 (Full Time). Approval to teach mathematics (Years 7 - 10), mathematics (Years 11 - 12) and legal studies. Willingness to teach legal studies. 20/06/2016 - 15/12/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=8491"</link>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teacher - Winston Hills Public School</title>
      <description>Years K - 6 (Full Time). Approval to teach infants (K - 2) and primary (3 - 6). 18/07/2016 - 20/12/2016.</description>
      <link>https://online.det.nsw.edu.au/schoolfind/locator/?do=showRecord&amp;code=4417"</link>
   </job>
</jobs>